xiamenair.com.cn 2014-05-19

# 厦门航空有限公司-Privacy Policy

Xiamen Airlines recognizes the importance of your privacy. Xiamen Airlines respects and protects your privacy. The Privacy Policy constitutes the contract by which you may access the services of Xiamen Airlines. You and Xiamen Airlines are both bound by the Policy.

In addition, we may post specific privacy notices to explain the treatment of personal information related to particular services when a more detailed explanation of our Privacy Policy is needed.

Xiamen Airlines adheres to the Chinese laws relating to Notice, Choice, Onward Transfer, Security, Data accuracy, Access and Execution.

Xiamen Airlines will treat your personal information in a responsible manner. The information you choose to provide to us will only be used to help us provide you with better service. If you have any questions about this Policy, please feel free to contact us as specified in our Website, or write to us at:  
Address: No. 22 Dailiao Road, Xiamen, China  
Postal Code: 361006  
Telephone: 86 -592-5739888  
Fax: 86 -592-5739777  
E-mail: [et@xiamenair.com.cn](mailto:et@xiamenair.com.cn)

Personal information we collect and how we use it

We offer a number of services that do not require you to register or provide any personal information to us, through which you can have anonymous access to services. However, to provide you with better service, we may collect the following types of information in the following ways when your personal information is needed for us to provide certain services:

1).Information you provide  
When you sign up for services or promotions that require registration, we may ask you for personal information (such as your name, postal address, date of birth, email address, occupation and an account password, which is conditional for using the website). For certain services, we may also request credit card or other payment account information which we maintain in encrypted form on secure servers. We may combine the information you submit with other information we know in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our services.

It is always your choice whether or not to provide personal information when you use the services of Xiamen Airlines. If you choose not to provide requested personal information, you will not be able to enjoy certain services. You must ensure that the information you provide is credible and accurate, and that no false, tortious or harmful information is involved. In some cases, we may use your email address or other personal information provided to communicate with you about our service materials or advertising. As we cannot know accurately whether or not you need specific information, we will send you the materials and information unless your explicitly rejection, you may refuse to receive or to delete such materials and information.

2).Cookie  
A cookie is a small file containing a string of characters that uniquely identifies your browser but does not collect personally identifiable information. When you visit Xiamen Airlines’ Website, we send one or more cookies to your computer. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends. Cookies also enable us to identify you as a previous or registered user when you return to our Website. Cookies from Xiamen Airlines’ Website can only be read by Xiamen Airlines. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some of Xiamen Airlines’ web services may not function properly if your computer refuses Xiamen Airlines’ cookies.

3).Site log information  
When you use Xiamen Airlines services, our servers may automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These records may include information such as your web request, Internet protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

4).User communications  
When you send email or other communication to Xiamen Airlines, we may retain this communication in order to process your inquiry, respond to your requests and improve our services.

5).Affiliated sites  
We offer some of our services in connection with other websites. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to Xiamen Airlines in order for us to deliver the service you requested. We process such information in accordance with this Policy. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and we suggest you to read their privacy policies. In addition, our Website may provide links to third party websites for your convenience. As we have no control over third party websites, we recommend that you read carefully the privacy policies of any of these websites.

We may also collect and use your personal information for: offering our products and services to users; auditing, research and analysis in order to improve our services; ensuring the technical functioning of our network; and developing new services. We will collect and use personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling these purposes through the methods specified in this Policy.

Privacy Protection

We will take appropriate measures to protect your privacy. When you provide us with personal information (particularly in relation to your medical information, racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious beliefs or affiliations, or sensitive gender-related information), we take appropriate measures to protect the security of such information, and we will not share any of your personal information with any unrelated third party without your consent.

We may share your personal information with other companies or individuals outside Xiamen Airlines only in the following limited circumstances:

a)We have your consent;

b)We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy, and take all other appropriate measures to ensure the confidentiality and security of our customers’ personal information;

c)We comply with the mandatory provisions of laws and regulations, and the compulsory acts of government and judicial authorities;

d)We find that you may be in violation of this provision or other terms of service Xiamen Airlines, or there are other possibilities that may damage our interests;

e)We need to act to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues;

f)We cannot provide the requested products and services unless your personal information is disclosed.

If at any time you believe that Xiamen Airlines has failed to comply with this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us as specified in the Privacy Policy or on our Website. We will adopt appropriate measures, where possible, to address the questions you raised immediately.

Accessing and Updating Personal Information

If your address, occupation, telephone number, email address or other personal information changes, you can access and update it using the links provided on our Website, so that we can keep your personal information accurate and up-to-date. In order to access and update confidential information, users must first identify themselves. We allow users to access and update their personal information as required, free of charge, except if doing so is unreasonably frequent or done with intent of malice, in which case, we reserve the right to limit access.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time without prior notice to you and an updated version may be released on the Xiamen Airlines’ Website at any time. For specific conditions in effect at any time, refer to the Website for the latest version of the Privacy Policy, which shall prevail.  
The Policy is effective as of August 12, 2011.
